let's take a look at two closely related
让我们来看看两个密切相关的
refactorings in IntelliJ IDEA called
IntelliJ IDEA中的重构称为
pull members up and push members down
向上拉成员，向下拉成员
and for the sir factoring I'm going to
对于先生保理，我要
enlist the help of the project structure
争取项目结构的帮助
view which I can bring up by pressing
按一下即可显示的视图
Alt 7 so you can see that I have some
Alt 7，这样您就可以看到我有一些
inner classes here and let's look
内部类，让我们看一下
carefully how these are laid out by
仔细地布置这些
selecting the parent class a and
选择父类a和
pressing ctrl H I can see that it has
按Ctrl HI可以看到它具有
three children b c and d which all
三个孩子BC和D
extend from a now if i'd like to a
如果我想从现在延长到
factor one or more of these methods in
将以下一种或多种方法考虑在内
the child class i can do that by
儿童班，我可以通过
selecting the methods in the editor and
在编辑器中选择方法，然后
pressing ctrl alt shift t to open the
按ctrl alt shift t打开
factor menu and then selecting pull
因素菜单，然后选择拉
members up i can choose exactly which
成员起来，我可以准确选择
methods i'd like to pull up by selecting
我想选择的方法
them and then hitting or factor now
他们然后打或现在因子
whenever we apply these types of
每当我们应用这些类型的
refactorings IntelliJ IDEA will search
重构IntelliJ IDEA将搜索
for any occurrences inside our code
对于我们代码中的任何出现
where it can replace a duplicate and if
在哪里可以替换重复项，如果
I select replace it will automatically
我选择替换它将自动
use the inherited method from the
使用从继承的方法
superclass
超类
here in these subclasses without me
在这些没有我的子类中
having to do anything else let's see
不得不做其他事情让我们看看
that one more time from the beginning
从头开始还有一个时间
you can see that this class B has three
您可以看到B类有三个
methods unbeknownst to C and D who have
C和D不知道的方法
already implemented similar methods as
已经实现了与
soon as you have factored these methods
一旦考虑了这些方法
by pulling them up into a IntelliJ IDEA
通过将它们拉入IntelliJ IDEA
will offer to replace those duplicate
将提供替换那些重复的
occurrences with a reference to the new
引用新的事件
inherited methods likewise there's a
继承的方法同样有一个
similar a factoring for pushing these
类似的因素推动了这些
member functions down into a subclass if
成员函数可以细分为子类
we select quiz members down and select
我们选择测验成员并选择
the members we'd like to push
我们想要推动的成员
then it will warn us of any potential
它将警告我们任何潜在的
conflicts and you see that all of the
冲突，您会看到所有
subclasses of a B C and D now have
BC和D的子类现在具有
separate implementations for each of
每个单独的实现
these methods removing the functionality
这些方法删除了功能
from our superclass
从我们的超类
so those are two refactorings that will
所以这是两个重构
come in handy when working with methods
使用方法时派上用场
inside a type hierarchy pull members up
在类型层次结构中拉成员
and push members down if you have any
如果有的话就把成员推倒
questions please feel free to add them
问题，请随时添加
in the comment section below and we'd be
在下面的评论部分，我们将
happy to discuss them with you thanks
很高兴与您讨论他们，谢谢
for watching and develop with pleasure
乐于观看和发展